<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on English</title><link>https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on English</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 17:41:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 17:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/overview/</guid><description>Concepts This chapter outlines the concepts and top level points required to understand and enjoy building on neo &amp;amp; NeoFS
Starting out You will need:
Go language installed and running Clone, or go get the libraries outlined below. Confirm you can import them into a project Read the wallets page as it will outline the basis of working with Neo and NeoFS - a wallet. Neo/Gas in your wallet. You can get these from the testnet faucet here These libraries will assume you are using the testnet throughout.</description></item><item><title>Libraries</title><link>https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:14:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/libraries/</guid><description>Code Libraries The Go SDK is the basis of all the functionality that is available to you as a developer with regards to NeoFS.
the Neo-Go package offers all the functionalities that you will require to interact with the Neo blockchain and wallets
SDK The SDK is responsible for providing functionality to interact with NeoFS itself via gRPC requests. You will need the SDK for such things as:
creating, retrieving, deleting containers creating, updating, retrieving, deleting objects creating basic and extended ACL rules for containers find it here Neo-Go library General interaction with NeoFS doesn&amp;rsquo;t require Neo-Go however invariably you will need to manage wallets or use cryptographic functions that are required while setting permissions throughout the NeoFS system.</description></item><item><title>Concepts</title><link>https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/concepts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neo-docs.onrender.com/introduction/concepts/</guid><description>NeoFS is very carefully designed to offer the power of a filesytem with all the expected capabilities, on top of a decentralised network.
This means that files/folders etc can have permissions to who can read/write to them who can delete etc etc.
As NeoFS is built on top of the Neo blockchain, these permissions are based on wallet addresses of users.
Objects Objects represent all files/data that is stored on NeoFS.</description></item></channel></rss>